One way to get your poetry published is to write and send it in to magazines.
Magazines sometimes will print poetry, and even sometimes will pay for poetry.
Another way is submit your pieces through anthology and collections.
Even if they don't pay, you're getting your poetry published into a book format.
And, usually, anthologies will give you at least one copy of the book, and then you buy extra copies for your friends and family.
If you have an entire book of poetry that you want to publish, you can go to a self publishing or subsidy press.
And for very little money, you can still have your poetry book, formatted in any way that you like, and with any kind of cover you want.
OK, this is one that a poet, she wanted it hard cover.
She was very specific on the colors that she wanted to use, as far as the interior purple.
With subsidy press and self publishing printing, you can decide all those things for yourself and have the book that you've always wanted.